tenorshare.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement | Tenorshare

Tenorshare fully respects your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about you without your clear permission. Any personal information which you volunteer to Tenorshare will be treated with the appropriate standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts, 1988 & 2003.

Collection and use of personal information

Tenorshare does not collect any personal data about you on this website or in connection with any other service, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us, by purchasing a product from us, by downloading a product from us, or by registering your product with us, or by using our online feedback form).

Information which you provide is used by Tenorshare only in line with the purpose for which you provided it and will not be made available to third parties, other than information provided to us during the purchase process which may be provided to our online billing provider and our banking institution to enable the purchase to be processed.

If Tenorshare has your email address, we may contact you by email to advise you of product updates, subscribe you to our newsletter or offer you Tenorshare or third party products. You can opt out from receiving these emails at any time. Tenorshare may also contact you in relation to customer support queries which you lodge.

About Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

Changes to this policy

Please note that Tenorshare may change this policy from time to time. Any amended policy terms will be posted to the Tenorshare website.

Question?

Please send any questions or comments on our privacy practices to **support#tenorshare.com** (replace # with @)
